{
    "subject": "Riazuddin__physicist_",
    "predicate": "worksAt",
    "object": "Pakistan_Atomic_Energy_Commission",
    "human_readable": "Riazuddin, the physicist, works at the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8502585291862488,
            "question": "What kind of work does the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.732631504535675,
            "question": "Where does Riazuddin work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7308010458946228,
            "question": "Who is Riazuddin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6764940619468689,
            "question": "Is Riazuddin associated with the field of physics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6500904560089111,
            "question": "What is the full name of the organization where Riazuddin works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5829082131385803,
            "question": "What profession does Riazuddin have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5699208974838257,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges facing the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4181384742259979,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Riazuddin's research?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3856219947338104,
            "question": "How does Riazuddin's work contribute to his field?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38145652413368225,
            "question": "Are there any notable achievements associated with Riazuddin's career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Riazuddin, the physicist, works at the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission.",
            "html": "yago_26556_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does Riazuddin's work contribute to his field?",
            "html": "yago_26556_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Riazuddin's research?",
            "html": "yago_26556_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the challenges facing the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission?",
            "html": "yago_26556_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26556_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26556_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26556_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26556_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26556_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26556_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26556_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26556_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26556_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26556_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Riazuddin was the director of the Theoretical Physics Group (TPG) of the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission (PAEC) from 1974 until 1984, which suggests that he works at the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Dr. Riazuddin worked at the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission (PAEC), specifically mentioning his role as the director of the Theoretical Physics Group (TPG) of PAEC from 1974 until 1984."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}